COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
This is good!
Bit by bit,
I'm figuring out the timing...
He read my movement.
No way could he do that!
Damn!
We were so close...!
Naruto, can you still move?
Of course! I'm totally fine!
He's pretty much spent...
and it's no wonder.
Shadow Clone Jutsu uses
a lot of Chakra.
But thanks to him,
we found our way out.
I found the way to break through!
Hah! Impossible!
That was just a coincidence.
Naruto! Run!
Run out of here and
attack from the outside!
A-All right!
You won't be able to...!
I-I'm not going to lose!
There!
Fire Style: Fire Ball Jutsu!
Damn!
T-That was good just now!
What?
We're doing it one more time!
All right!
It's likely that there's a limit
to that guy's Chakra, too!
To prove that,
he's little by little...
This won't go as you've planned.
First, I'll get you!
Sasuke!
Damn! It's been a while since
I've fought in such bad conditions.
And I'm worried about
Sasuke and Naruto, too...
Be calm... Think...
What will he come after?
Oh no!
What?!
Too late!
The Seal
that has Been Released
That was Sakura's voice!
Did something happen?
What's that Kakashi doing?
Sa... kura... chan...
Damn it... I must do something...
I'll do something about it...
T-This guy...
Here I go...
It's pointless to struggle.
Naruto, behind you!!
Naruto!
It's impossible for you
to get out of here.
I mean it.
Can you stand up, Naruto?
Y-Yeah...
From now on,
don't waste your Chakra!
You're playing right into his hands.
I know.
Damn it!
If things continue like this,
it's going to be really bad.
I...
I have to do something.
Strangely, my eyes have adjusted...
It's about the time I put
an end to this for you...
What?!
Stand up, you idiot!
I'm aiming for a vital spot...
but he's parrying all of them .
I know...
you're so persistent!
A coincidence...
No, that's not it.
On the contrary, he's fighting
while covering for his friend.
Surely, my movements...
That boy... he can see something.
What in the world...?
Okay, in that case...
He disappeared.
Where, where did he disappear to?!
Naruto! Don't faint!
I can't take care of you
any more than I am now!
Who asked you to take care of me...
It seems that kid has
reached his limits.
Tsk...
Amazing...
That's an amazing move.
You move well...
Wha...?!
But I'll stop you
with the next one.
Motor function...
Reflexes...
Ability to judge a situation...
All of these things...
should be at their limits!
He's coming!
Calm down...
Focus!
And...
See everything!
He saw through absolutely everything?!
No way...
Those eyes...
It can't be...
Sharingan...
You are...
Only a little, but...
I was able to see!
So, you also have the power
of Kekkei Genkai...
What a kid...
It's not perfect yet,
but to think that in the middle of a battle
he was able to rouse this power...
If that's the case,
I can't fight him too long...
This Jutsu uses a lot of Chakra.
There are also limits to retaining
the teleportation speed.
Besides, the longer the fight continues,
the more my movements will enter
into the range of his "reading."
In fact, his eyes
have already captured me.
It would be foolish to aim
straight at him.
In that case...
I'll use that kid to lure him in!
What?!
Let me make it in time!
Kakashi-sensei!
You were late entering
to guard, Kakashi.
Your whole-hearted intent to help
those kids has gone to your head,
and it seems to have clouded
your Sharingan
with even heavier fog.
Even though you have
those impressive eyes,
your ability to read your enemy's
movements is getting cloudy.
Amuse me more, Kakashi...
I want to repay my debt in
an amusing way.
Don't worry. Anytime now,
Haku is going to defeat those kids.
You better apologize to them
in tears
when you are in "the next world"
for your lack of strength.
Sasuke-kun will be defeated...?
That's not true!
Sasuke-kun is...
Shannaro!
Not by that guy!
He won't be defeated!
Shannaro!
Naruto won't either!
That's right.
Huh!
I... believe in their strength.
Naruto is the Number One Hyperactive,
Knucklehead Ninja...
And Sasuke is a member of
the most excellent clan
in the Hidden Leaf Village!
That can't be!
Yes...
His name is Uchiha Sasuke...
He bears within his body...
the famous Kekkei Genkai
of the Uchiha clan!
He's a Ninja genius.
He's the remaining survivor
of that tragic clan?!
No wonder he grows so quickly.
But...
That's the same as Haku.
Nobody has ever beaten
that secret Jutsu of Haku's
Not one person in the past...
Well then...
It's about time I settled this too, huh.
Sakura, don't move from here.
Uh... ah... okay!
No, I'm going to put
an end to this!
For God's sake, you...
just won't quit...
dragging my feet, will you?
You did it!
Sasuke...!
W-What kind of expression
is that...
You... idiot...!
W-Why?!
You protected me...?!
How the hell... should I know?
Sasuke...! Sasuke...! Sasuke...!
Hmph...
You...
I hated you...
Why? Why...?
Why... me...?
I didn't ask for your help!!
I don't know...
My body moved... of its own accord...
Fool...!
Sasuke!
That man...
Until I defeated... my brother...
I absolutely refused to die...
That's what I decided, but...
You, don't die...
He...
To protect someone dear to him...
he would plunge in
knowing it was a trap...
He's a Shinobi worthy of respect.
Is this the first time you faced
a friend's death?
This is the way of the Shinobi...
Shut up!
Even though I...
hated you too...
I won't forgive you...
I'm going to kill you!
What is this Chakra?!
It can't be...
For Chakras to be tangible like that...
A-And... what a ghastly Chakra that is...
The wound on his hand...
It's healing instantly...
This boy...
Who in hell is he...?
Is it Zabuza...?
No!
This sinister Chakra was once...
It can't be!
What is... this Chakra?
It feels foul...
Kakashi?
No, it's too big to be Kakashi's...
Who is it?
Naruto...!
Oh no...
At the time like this...
The seal has broken...?
I have to hurry!
He's coming!
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
How dare you!
You ruined Sasuke!
Damn you!
Sasuke's dream...
What about your dream?!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Because of your dream...!
Next time:
"The White Past. The Secret Feelings."